tickerbar.info 2018-12-25

# TickerBar - It's ALWAYS a Sure Bet! (A Non-Complicated Paid to Surf Program)

## Green Horse Corporation Privacy Policy

The web site TickerBar.info is registered, owned and operated by Manchester, New Hampshire based Green Horse Corporation. Upon registration our members are required to provide full name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number And password. This information is used to manage the access to sensitive member-specific information such as account balance, member profile, and eligibility for certain services and benefits provided by Green Horse and its affiliates. Members' correct full name and postal address are required for consistent payment processing. Email address is required to provide user login and/or value-added services. In addition, we require user-specific information such as interests, gender, age, household income, and education, which is used to build member profiles that are used for the purposes of targeted advertising and benefit distribution. 

Green Horse will not share, sell, trade, or give away personally identifiable member information to third parties without members' explicit permission. Upon registration, all users grant to Green Horse their explicit permission (1) to contact them with important information about members' accounts and updates to our services, policies and business practices, and (2) to share members' information with third parties. The users have the option to choose not to be contacted or their information shared by terminating their account. At any given time, Green Horse members can change their user profiles by utilizing the provided functionality in the "User Info" section of the Green Horse web site. Green Horse and its affiliates work with many different advertising companies, including advertisers, brokers, agencies, affiliates, and networks. These companies may use information (not including your name, address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services of interest to you. Once the user visits an advertiser, Green Horse is not responsible for the information exchanged between the user and the advertiser. We encourage users to read the privacy statements of these entities as their privacy policy may differ from ours. 

**Opt-in Program**

By checking to receive commercial (opt-in) email, you are allowing us to share your information with our marketing partners so that they can send you information about products and services, which may be of interest to you. These partners may include direct marketing service providers for promotions and lookup and reference applications. You may opt-out of receiving these messages at a later date by following the opt-out procedures. 

**Cookies**

Cookies are tiny text files written on a user's computer. Green Horse uses cookies to customize ad stream services for Green Horse and its affiliates. As per our Terms of Service, upon registration, all users grant to Green Horse their explicit permission to create and manage cookies to personally identify members and render its services. The users have the option to decline cookies by changing the security setting of their browser, by deleting cookie files, and by terminating their Green Horse account. We use third-party companies to serve advertising content. This advertising may contain third party cookies and we do not have control over and/or access to this information.   
We use a proprietary system for ad delivery and ad stream management. For more information about cookies, our members may visit http://www.cookiecentral.com. 

**Children and Privacy**

We do not consider our Web site to be directed at children under the age of thriteen. To register with Green Horse users must be thirteen (13) years of age or older. 

**Security**

Green Horse Corporation has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We use industry standard procedures and processes, such as firewall, proxies, encryption and monitoring to prevent abuse of our network and its data. Access to user's data is limited to Database Administrators and Customer Service Representatives only. There are several measures implemented to control access to the data, based on login passwords, NT and Unix file access permissions, and IP address permissions.  
For questions regarding the specific security measures in place, please contact us at privacy@Green Horse.info. In terms of safety, we suggest that users protect their account passwords, log out, and close their browser and our toolbar when away from the computer. 

**Choice/Opt-Out**

Green Horse Corporation provides users the opportunity not to choose to receive commercial email from our advertisers during registration. There are a couple of options for permanently removing members' information from our database systems: 

  1. Go to Account Information/Terminate your account 
  2. Go to Members Area/User Info and uncheck the Subscribe for commercial (opt-in) email box at any time after registration. 

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on our homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point, we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users via e-mail. Users will be offered whether or not we can use their information in a different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.  
For questions regarding this privacy statement, or the practices of this site, please send an email to privacy@Green Horse.info or write to: Green Horse Corporation  
P.O. Box 195  
Manchester, NH 03105-0195  

TickerBar™ offers its members the ability to get paid just for using the internet. 

©2002 - 2015 Green Horse Corporation. All Rights Reserved.
